

ROHAN ADHIA

DATA ANALYST

Highly analytical and process-oriented data analyst with in-depth knowledge of database types; research methodologies; and big data capture, curation, manipulation and visualization. Furnish insights, analytics and business intelligence used to advance opportunity identification, process reengineering and corporate growth.

CONTACT

- Andheri East, Mumbai-400069
- rohanadhia@gmail.com
- +91 9930494215
- in /rohanadhia

PERSONAL PROFILE

Extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally. I am confident in my excellent technical abilities, as they are responsible for evaluating sets of information and implementing appropriate solutions. My applicable technical experience and skills can include the following: programming and coding; ability to translate unstructured information into structured information

EDUCATION

Business Analytics & Data Science(2019) Edupristine

Ignite Program(2017)

Datamatics Business Solutions Limited

Bachelor of Science Information Technology (2014-15) Malini Kishor Sanghvi College of Commerce & Economics

Higher Secondary School (2010 – 2011) Vidyanidhi Jr. College

Secondary School Certificate (2007-2008)

St. Dominic Savio High School

SKILLS AND EXPERTISE

Excellent technical abilities, strong interpersonal skills, and effective project management abilities.

LANGUAGES & TECHNOLOGY

- Data Analytics using R language.
- Python
- Java,
- ASP.NET with C#
- C & C++
- · Google App Script -(Based on Javascript
- used to automate day to day tasks.)
- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- Front End Framework(Bootstrap)

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- GRAPHIC DESIGNING Logo Designs
 Social Media Post Design
 Website Designing,
 Visiting Card Design
 Poster Design ..etc.-
- Music Production using FL Studio

HOBBIES

- Designing
- Music Production
- Reading
- · Web development
- · Watching web-series

- Node JS JS Runtime Environment
- Express JS JS Framework for Node JS
- JQuery
- · APIs & Interfaces

SOFTWARES

- MS Excel & Google Sheets
- R Software
- MS office
- Adobe Photoshop
- · Adobe Illustrator
- Visual Studio
- Canva
- Github

WORK EXPERIENCE

Angel Broking, Specialist - Analytics

SEPT 2018 - PRESENT

- Collaborating data from various branches & regions to ensure streamlined implementations of services, profiling source information and setting characteristics, and executing big data processes like parsing, filtering, text connotation, and enrichment.
- Responsible to look after business and financial data for the branch.
- Developed a live sales dashboard used for real time tracking and analysis of sales
- Mapping of client based on their region
- Analysis of various types sales and brokerage data for PAN india
- Designing and making analytical presentation for board meetings
- Automation of data to generate reports .

WNS Global Services, Senior Associate - Operations

SEPT 2017 - AUG 2018

- Responded to customer service enquiries/ complaints/suggestions/feedback via email within the assigned TAT.
- Identified and highlighted any concern affecting the brand.
- Provided accurate, valid and complete information by using the right methods and tools.

Datamatics Business Solutions Limited, Associate Web Research

JAN 2016 - MARCH 2017

- Worked on various projects into Data Research, Data Mining, & Data Cleansing
- Client interaction on regular basis
- Worked majorly with pilot projects & FTE projects
- Sampled data for new clients & provided efficient solutions working with the solutions desk
- Nominated & certified the Ignite program